ixiacom.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy | Ixia

Customers are Ixia's, a Keysight Buisness, most valuable asset. We recognize that building a long-term business relationship with you depends a great deal on trust. This trust begins with our commitment to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement provides a clear and prominent explanation of how we collect, use, share and protect your personal data.

These areas are described in detail below. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third-party websites, services and applications that you elect to access through our websites.

Comments or questions about our privacy practices can be sent to Ixia's, a Keysight Buisness [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com").

* **Types of Personal Data We Collect**

Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, including information that can be used to identify you as an individual, directly or indirectly by reference to one or more factors specific to you. Personal data can include the following types of information:

**Personal information** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, collects and uses personal information from our customers and potential customers. Such information includes your name, contact information (postal address, telephone number, fax number, and email address), billing information, transaction history and credit card or other financial information. You may also elect to provide Ixia, a Keysight Business with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences.

**Online usage information** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, also sometimes collects and uses information from your online interactions with us. Online usage information can include IP address, browser size, type and language, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of visits to our website and the hyperlinks you visited.

We may combine the information you provide to us through different communications and contact channels, for example by combining data collected online with information provided offline.

* **How We Collect Personal Data**

Ixia, a Keysight Business, collects personal information in several ways. We collect personal information that you choose to provide Ixia, a Keysight Business on [ixiacom.com](https://www.ixiacom.com/ "https://www.ixiacom.com"), in person, on the phone or electronically. Additionally, we may now or in the future receive personal information about you from third parties that legally acquired the information and that have the right to share it with Ixia, a Keysight Business. For example, we may receive contact information from a relevant trade show or event sponsor.

Ixia, a Keysight Business, uses cookies and other technologies such as web beacons, local shared objects, local storage, e-tags, and JavaScript, to collect online usage information. Please review Ixia's, a Keysight Buisness [Cookie Policy](https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy "https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy") for more information regarding Ixia's use of these technologies and your choices about them.

* **How We Use the Personal Data We Collect**

**Use of personal information** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, uses your personal information: (a) to respond to your correspondence; (b) to help you complete a transaction or order; (c) to provide updates on service and benefits; (d) to personalize our website for your needs; (e) to provide advertising, promotions or newsletters regarding Ixia, a Keysight Business products and services to you online or by email; (f) to conduct market research to help us better meet our customers’ needs; (g) to obtain your feedback on Ixia, a Keysight Business, products or services you have purchased; (h) to comply with Ixia's legal obligations, including export controls and trade compliance laws; and (i) for payment and order processing. Whenever we collect credit card numbers or other financial data, such information will be encrypted, will only be used for payment processing and will not be retained for other purposes. 

**Use of online usage information** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, collects online usage information to optimize your online experience, specifically: (a) to remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) to provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) to provide and monitor the effectiveness of our website; (d) to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) to diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) to help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (g) to provide advertising for Ixia, a Keysight Business, products and services to you online or by email. 

**Use of combined personal data** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, may sometimes combine your personal information with online usage information to build a broader profile of our individual users so that we can better serve our customers. This combined data will be used only for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement.

**Online advertising** : We partner with trusted third parties to manage Ixia, a Keysight Business, advertising on other websites. These partners use cookies to collect information about your activities on Ixia's website, so that we can provide you advertising for Ixia, a Keysight Business, products and services that are relevant to your interests. For more information about third-party cookies and online advertising, please review Ixia's, a Keysight Buisness [Cookie Policy](https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy "https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy").

* **How We Share Your Personal Data**

**Personal information** : Ixia, a Keysight Business, will not rent or sell your personal information to parties. We will only share your personal information outside of Ixia, a Keysight Business, for the reasons described below:

**Ixia, a Keysight Business, business partners:** We may share your personal information with Ixia, a Keysight Business, business partners including sales, rental and solution partners and agents offering Ixia, a Keysight Business products and services, and vendors acting at our direction. We do so only to the extent necessary for the specific business partnership, or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. Such Ixia, a Keysight Business business partners are required to keep this information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to offer, sell or rent Ixia, a Keysight Business products and services, or to provide services at Ixia's direction.

**Corporate transactions:** Circumstances may arise where Ixia, a Keysight Business, decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of such information from sellers. It is Ixia's practice to disclose personal information in these circumstances only as permitted by applicable data protection law and to seek appropriate protection for personal information in these types of corporate transactions.

**Legal necessity:** Ixia, a Keysight Business also may disclose your personal information: (a) if we are required to do so by law; (b) if we believe that it is necessary to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements or otherwise protect and defend the rights, property or safety of Ixia, a Keysight Business or that of our customers; or (c) to comply with a judicial proceeding, bankruptcy proceeding, court order or other legal obligation or government inquiry

**Your consent:** Ixia, a Keysight Business also may disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.

**Online usage information:** We may share online usage information: (a) in any manner permitted for personal information; and (b) with vendors or service providers for the purposes described in the section above on “How We Use the Personal Data We Collect.” We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated, anonymized data with third parties. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal information.

**User content:** Ixia, a Keysight Business provides some opportunities for you to generate your own internet-based content about Ixia, a Keysight Business and our products and services. Typically, the personal information that you provide in this user content will be shared outside of Ixia, a Keysight Business as described below.

**User-generated comments:** Ixia's website may contain areas where users can transmit or post communications, for example, on blogs or in user forums. Any personal information you submit there will be publicly available, and can be read, collected or used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in such public areas.

**Social media widgets:** Ixia's website may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, widgets such as the “Share This” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These features may collect online usage information through cookies or web beacons. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the social media company providing them.

**Testimonials:** Ixia, a Keysight Business sometimes posts on our website customer testimonials that may contain personal information. We obtain our customers’ consent to post their name or other personal information along with their testimonial prior to posting the testimonial on our website. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please contact Ixia's, a Keysight Business [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com").

* **How We Store, Process and Protect Your Personal Data**

**Storage and processing of your personal data:** Ixia's global organizational structure requires the global transfer of personal data within the Ixia group of companies. As a result, we may transfer personal data to, and store or process personal data in, countries other than the country in which the personal data originally was collected. Those countries may not have as comprehensive data protection laws as the country from which Ixia, a Keysight Business initially obtained the personal data. However, Ixia, a Keysight Business has executed agreements between and among Ixia, a Keysight Business entities operating in different countries that contain Standard Contractual Clauses (“SCCs”) as defined in the E.U. Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC) and as further authorized in the E.U. General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) Article 46(5), to ensure that adequate safeguards are in place for the protection of personal data. Therefore, when we transfer, store or process personal data in other countries, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with the SCCs and this Privacy Statement.

**Data Retention:** We retain your personal data as part of your individual customer record for a period of five years following any activity on your account. After that time, your record will be inactivated and then deleted in accordance with Ixia's data retention practices. We may retain personal data associated with orders, quotes, or other official business records for a longer period of time as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security:** Ixia, a Keysight Business puts in place appropriate physical, electronic and organizational measures to safeguard and secure your data. These measures follow generally accepted industry standards both during transmission and once it is received. Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmission to our website.

**Data compromise:** In the event that your personal data under our control is compromised, Ixia, a Keysight Business will investigate the situation and take all steps required by applicable law.  This includes notification of the competent data protection authority where applicable, and when appropriate notification of those individuals whose personal data may have been compromised. Ixia, a Keysight Business, a may take other steps in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

* **Your Rights and Choices About Your Personal Data**

You have certain rights with respect to your personal data, including: the right to information about the personal data we store about you, the right to have your personal data corrected if it is inaccurate, and the right to object, on grounds relating your particular situation, at any time to processing of your personal data. You also have the right, under certain circumstances, to erasure, restriction of processing, and portability of your personal data. 

To exercise your rights please contact Ixia's. a Keysight Business [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com"). We will respond to your request as soon as is reasonably practicable and in any event within 30 days. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. Additional ways you may exercise choice about your personal data are outlined below.

**Opting out of collection of personal information:** You may, of course, decline to submit any personal information to Ixia, a Keysight Business, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some features of our website and we may not be able to communicate with you about Ixia, a Keysight Business products and services. In addition, personal information may be required to determine access eligibility for certain restricted parts of our website.

**Opting out of collection of online usage information:** Your browser or mobile device may allow you to delete and disable cookies. Note that disabling cookies may disable many of the features available through Ixia's website. Please refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy "https://www.ixiacom.com/cookie-policy") for more information about any choices you may have with respect to cookies and the other technologies we may use to collect online usage information.

**Opting out of Ixia** **  emails: **You may choose to opt out of receiving marketing emails from Ixia, a Keysight Business, including newsletters and promotions by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each marketing email or by contacting Ixia's, a Keysight Business [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com"). However, please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or special offers. If you opt out of marketing emails, we may continue to send you transaction or service-related emails about our business dealings with you to the extent required to establish, carry out or terminate such business dealings. We reserve the right to contact you for non-promotional purposes when we believe it is necessary, including where required by law. If you have any difficulty exercising your choices or feel that choices you made on particular websites have not been taken into account, please use Ixia's [unsubscribe form](http://ixinfo.ixiacom.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple "http://ixinfo.ixiacom.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple").

**Opting out of advertising:** Both [TRUSTe](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/ "https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/") and the [National Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/") provide mechanisms that allow you to opt out of receiving targeted advertising (i.e., advertising that is tailored to your interests based on your online browsing activities) from certain advertising providers. You also may opt out directly with [Google](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/ "https://www.google.com/settings/ads/") and [Adobe](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html "https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html"). For customers in the E.U., you also may opt-out through the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ "https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/").

Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising altogether. You will continue to see generic ads.

**Deletion of user content:** To request that Ixia, a Keysight Business remove your user content or personal information from public areas of our website, contact Keysight’s [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com"). In some instances, we may not be able to remove your user content or personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. In addition, such information may continue to be available online even after it is removed from our website.

* **Additional Information**

**Other websites:** We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from Ixia's website including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go outside Ixia's website, our Privacy Statement does not apply to third-party websites or services. Ixia, a Keysight Business is not responsible for and does not control any third parties that you authorize to access your user content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook) and you allow such a third party access to your user content, you do so at your own risk.

**Dispute Resolution:** If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, you should first contact Keysight’s Privacy Advocate If you believe that the collection or processing of your personal data by Ixia, a Keysight Business is not compliant with applicable data protection laws, or have a privacy or data use concern you may also contact the data protection authority in your country of residence. You can also contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

* **Changes to Our Privacy Statement**

This Privacy Statement is effective as of the date stated at the start of this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time by posting the revised statement on our website and updating the date the statement was last revised. If we make material changes to our privacy practices, we will notify you by email or by means of a prominent notice on our home page.

* **How to Contact Us**

Please contact Ixia's, a Keysight Buisness [Privacy Advocate](mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com "mailto:privacy_advocate@keysight.com") with questions or comments about our privacy practices at:

Keysight Technologies, Inc.  
1400 Fountaingrove Parkway  
Mailstop 1USM  
Santa Rosa, CA 95403  
United States

  Phone:  (707) 577-5030
